Ali Shabani

Front-End Developer



■ ali.shabani7811@gmail.com

+98-933-281-7811

Tehran, Iran

@ lamshabani.ir

in Ali Shabani

SKILLS

- Typescript, Javascript
- · ReactJS, NextJS
- Material UI, Antd
- Tailwind css, Shadcn/ui
- Redux, Redux Toolkit
- Git
- Monorepo
- Linux (Debian Based)
- HTML/CSS

ANGUAGES

English

Persian (native)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science: Computer Engineering

Sirjan University of Technology ☑ 2016 – 2021 | Sirjan, Iran

PROFILE

Front-End developer with more than 4 years of experience working with the React library. Interested in learning new topics in the field of web development and using them in the projects. Keen on reviewing code from successful projects and getting ideas to implement in my own projects.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Kuknos Co 🛮

Front end Developer

October 2021 - present

- Developed digital Rial management panel for Post Bank, Shahr, Pasargad, Dey Banks and others using Next.js, Shadon, and TailwindCSS, with a monorepo setup.
- Developed Kuknos Wallet ☑ (PWA) based on the Stellar Network using ReactJS, MUI v5 and Typescript.
- Developed Authentication and digital Certificate system (Sejel PWA) using NextJS v14, MUI v6 and Typescript.
- Developed decentralized trading platform (DEX
 Description based on the Stellar Network which the user can connect to (her/his) Kuknos wallet using Wallet Connect. using ReactJS and Ant design.
- Developed Crowdfunding ☑ platform (CF) based on the Stellar Network using ReactJS and Ant design.
- Designed and Developed Kuknos management panel (BackOffice ☑) using ReactJS and Tailwind css.
- Developed online election system (Aramesh ☑) based on the Stellar Network using HTML, CSS, Ant design, and ReactJS.

Freelance worker

Front end Developer

2019 - 2021

- Designed and Developed the website of AtlasKavir ☑ using HTML, CSS, MUI, and ReactJS, which specializes in agricultural products.
- Developed the website of Nafis Fabric ☑ using HTML, Tailwind css, Next.js v12 and Typescript. which provides fabric selling.
- Developed an Online Market named JimboMarket using HTML, CSS, Material UI, ReactJS.